The polarity field brings about the notochordal process.
极性场带来脊索过程。
This notochordal process influences the neuronal system.
这个脊索过程影响神经系统。
This neuronal system will influence the cardiac system,
这个神经系统将会影响心脏系统，
which itself, in a way, leads to the establishment at the diaphragmatic level,
它本身以某种方式带来膈肌层面的形成，
at the level of the septum transversum, thus the diaphragmatization,
在横膈膜平面上，也就是膈肌化，
which leads to the development of my adrenal glands.
这导致肾上腺的发育。
This is a movement that happens here, and then here there is the
这是一个发生在这里的运动，然后这里有
future development for my
我未来的发育
adrenal glands, okay, by the growth of the liver here, it will create a suction field here, I
肾上腺。好的，通过肝脏在这里的生长，会形成一个吸引场，这里我有肝脏。
have the liver.
我有肝脏。
And it will create a posterior space here in the posterior parietal peritoneum, and it's by
这将在这里的后腹膜壁层创造一个后部空间，
this
这是通过
growth that you will see at the posterior part here, like a suction field that
这种生长，你将会在这里的后部看到一个吸引场，它
will give these adrenal glands that become very, very large, they are there because they
将会形成非常大的肾上腺，它们在那里是因为它们
They also have this genetic information in the tissue.
它们在组织中也拥有这种遗传信息。
Initially, the urogenital system means that there are cells
首先，泌尿生殖系统导致有细胞
that are around my vitelline vesicle here.
在我卵黄囊的周围。
You see, that is, there is a migration of gonocytes coming from the vitelline vesicle
你看，也就是说有生殖细胞从卵黄囊迁移而来，
and which come to this part to colonize what we call
并且来到这一部分定植我们所称的
the genital ridge.
生殖嵴。
At the posterior wall, these small gonocytes come to swell this epithelium.
在后壁层面，这些小生殖细胞使这个上皮膨胀。
They inform this epithelium by a suction field, and this epithelium
通过一个吸引场来影响这个上皮，而这个上皮
that was there, all of a sudden begins to thicken and form a gonadal ridge.
原本在那里，突然开始增厚并形成生殖腺嵴。
But above, on the side, I have, through the liver and through this development, my adrenal glands that grow and
但是，在上方，在侧面，通过肝脏和这种发育，我的肾上腺在生长并
which push my gonads to the side.
推动我的性腺向侧面。
These are the gonads, these are my adrenal glands, on both sides, left and right.
这是性腺，这是我的肾上腺，在两侧，左边和右边。
By this movement of your mind, it comes to push.
通过这种心智运动，它来推动。
Here, it will create a lateral fold by the movement of
在这里，通过...的运动，这将创造一个侧向褶皱
my adrenal glands pushing the gonads.
我的肾上腺推动性腺。
It will create a fold in the tissue, because it does like this.
这将在组织中创造一个褶皱，因为它就像这样。
Adrenal glands, kidneys, those, this is the ovarian zone, it's the genital ridge,
肾上腺，肾脏，那些，这是卵巢区域，这是生殖嵴，
you see here.
你在这里看到。
Initially, this line here represents what we call the Müllerian
最初，这里这条线代表我们所说的导管，
duct.
苗勒氏。
A kind of fold like that, in the parietal peritoneum.
像这样的一种褶皱，在壁腹膜中。
posterior. A fold on the left and on the right. At this stage, there is no
后方。左右各一个褶皱。在这个阶段，还没有
difference
区别
yet between male and female. In females, on a structural level,
男性与女性之间。在女性中，在结构层面上，
it's already
这已经
done at the genetic level, the adrenal glands are more important, more developed
在基因层面完成，肾上腺更重要，更发达，
and therefore push the lateral movement more strongly. We
因此更强劲地推动侧向运动。我们
see a fold appearing in the tissue here
在这里看到组织中出现一个褶皱，
by this movement. And this kind of fold here,
通过这个运动。而这里这种褶皱，
laterally, it will give the fallopian tubes
侧向地，这将形成输卵管，
on the left and on the right
左右
but in the middle here
但在中间这里
I have the reunion
我看到汇合
by my liver which is now pulling in this tilt
通过我的肝脏，它现在拉动这种倾斜运动，
and bringing everything together like this
并像这样将一切带回，
and at the same time, I will have
同时，我将会有
my lower limbs
我的下肢
that start to come out here
在这里开始伸出
and so it creates a line here
因此这在这里创造了一条线
and a movement on the median line
和一个在中线上的运动，
you see these two tubes here, come together like this
你看这里这两个管子，像这样汇合，
you see
你看，
and the reunion of the two
而两者的汇合，
by the liver, organized by the liver above, which energizes
通过肝脏，由上方的肝脏组织，它驱动
the adrenal glands, which pushes more
肾上腺，它更强劲地推动
strongly my lateral gonads, and by this movement, creates this line here. But
我的侧向性腺，并通过这个运动，在这里创造了这条线。但是
above, the liver
上方，肝脏
comes back to pull with the opening of the same here above, and the reunion of the two, of the
被拉回，开口也在此处上方，而这两者的汇合，这两
two
个
tubes here, will form the uterus. In men, the difference is that this canal, it
条管子在此处，将形成子宫。在男性中，不同之处在于这条管道，它
regresses,
退化，
but in fact, it doesn't go that far.
但实际上，它不会延伸那么远。
It doesn't happen.
它没有形成。
You see, in women, it closes.
你看，在女性中，它会闭合。
And what does that give?
那这会形成什么呢？
It gives the fallopian tube.
它形成了输卵管。
And here, you will have the gonad developing,
而在这里，你将看到性腺正在发育，
which will later become the ovary and will make its space through here, you see, and through here.
它之后会发育成卵巢，并在此处和此处形成其空间，你明白吗？
The uterus is made of posterior parietal peritoneum.
子宫是后壁腹膜的一部分。
All of this, what is it?
所有这些是什么？
It's my broad ligament.
这是我的阔韧带。
With lines inside here which will be the ovarian ligament
内部有线条，它们将是卵巢韧带
or the uterosacral ligament.
或子宫骶韧带。
or the broad ligament, but in fact, it's all posterior parietal peritoneum.
或大的松弛韧带，但实际上，它都是后壁腹膜。
So, firstly, there is this migration.
所以，首先，存在这种迁移。
I have the genital ridge that is informed, that develops.
我有生殖嵴，它被告知并正在发育。
This genital ridge, with the adrenal glands here just before,
这个生殖嵴，伴随着此处之前存在的肾脏汗腺，
is connected to the development of the liver.
它与肝脏的发育相关联。
The development of the liver creates a new retroperitoneal space.
肝脏的发育创造了一个新的腹膜后空间。
This suction field, because it's a gland, so it's a tissue.
这个吸引场，因为它是一个腺体，所以它是一种组织。
which is aspirated, as we had seen for all glands.
它被吸引，就像我们之前看到的所有腺体一样。
It comes to push my gonads, the kidneys, it will make the mesonephros disappear.
它会推动我的性腺、肾脏，并使中肾消失。
However, my gonadal ridge pushes more and more laterally,
然而，我的性腺嵴越来越向外侧生长，
and the system does this, and creates a fold in the posterior parietal peritoneum.
系统会这样做，并在后壁腹膜中形成一个褶皱。
And this tube will be called the Müllerian tubercle.
而这条管子，它将被称为米勒氏结节。
While the first level that came from this collecting tube,
而第一个层面，它来自这个集合管，
which we call the mesonephric duct,
被称为中肾管，
it's called the Wolffian duct. That one is already there. It
它被称为沃尔夫管。它已经存在了。它
will serve as a conduit later for my gonadal ridge,
以后将作为我的生殖嵴的导管，
so future testicle or future ovaries, with the diaphragmatic suspensory ligament
即未来的睾丸或卵巢，连同膈悬韧带，
and below the gubernaculum
并在下方有引带，
which will guide to bring the ovaries back into
它将引导卵巢回到
their place according to this,
它们根据此而定的位置，
or in men, bring it back to the inguinal canal and the patients.
或者在男性中，将其带到腹股沟管的水平，以及患者。
in the pants.
到裤子里。